Guide to the Time Inc. Magazine Development Group Records 1967-1987, 2003 MS 3009-RG 40
New-York Historical Society
- Series I.B.5. 1973 to 1978 Business and Publishing: Business Manager Paul Hale Files, 1969-1978; 6.3 Linear feet in 8 record cartons
  - Subseries I.B.5.f. People, 1974-1977; 0.5 Linear feet in 1 record carton
    Includes Paul Hale's files on People, primarily focused on strategic planning.
    - Advertising, 1977 (Offsite-box 3734, Folder 4)
    - Strategic Planning: Forecast, 1974-1975 (Offsite-box 3734, Folder 5)
    - Strategic Planning: Preliminary Two-Year Plan, 1974? (Offsite-box 3734, Folder 6)
    - Strategic Planning: Two-Year Plan, 1974-1976 (Offsite-box 3734, Folder 7-9)
    - Strategic Planning: Two-Year Plan: Allocations, 1976 (Offsite-box 3734, Folder 10)
    - Weekly Reports, 1974-1975 (Offsite-box 3734, Folder 11-12)
  - Subseries I.B.5.g. Women's Magazine, 1976-1977; 1 Linear feet in 3 record cartons
    Hale, along with Stephen LaRue and Mary Davis, has the majority of records on the women's magazine including his copies of memoranda to and from editorial. Woman is how his records usually refer to the women's magazine since this is the title the MDG ultimately wanted to use. Later materials use this as a working title. Earlier records call it the woman's magazine, the women's magazine, Project "X" or "W".
    The business side worked extensively on the women's magazine beginning in mid-1976 on determining the ideal dummy size, trademark research, costs, and possible revenues. The file on background contains a copy of the 1975 prospectus written by Otto Fuerbringer who initially led editorial with assistance from Patricia Ryan. The file on editorial discusses focus group results. Research and Studies contain additional focus group results along with Ryan's and Kelso Sutton's thoughts on the idea of a women's magazine. Final Work files at the end contain more comments on the dummies from staff and focus group. In early 1978 when the MDG closed, work on the women's magazine was still underway.
    Restricted material includes agreements or contracts with Time Inc. as a party.
    Organized alphabetically with "Final Work" files at the end.
    - Administration and Profits and Losses, 1976 (Offsite-box 3734, Folder 13)
    - Advertising, 1976 (Offsite-box 3734, Folder 14)
    - Background, 1975-1976 (Offsite-box 3734, Folder 15)
    - Circulation, 1976 (Offsite-box 3734, Folder 16)
    - Dummy Budget, 1976 (Offsite-box 3734, Folder 17)
    - Editorial, 1976 (Offsite-box 3734, Folder 18)
    - Production, 1976 (Offsite-box 3734, Folder 19)
    - Research and Studies, 1976 (Offsite-box 3734, Folder 20-21)
    - Research and Studies, 1976 (Offsite-box 3735, Folder 1)
    - Sterling Forest Meeting, 1976 (Offsite-box 3735, Folder 2-3)
    - Final Work, 1977 (Offsite-box 3735, Folder 4-10)
    - Final Work [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Offsite-box R68)
- Series I.B.6. 1973 to 1978 Business and Publishing: Assistant Business Manager Mary Davis Files, 1976-1977; 0.75 Linear feet in 3 record cartons
  Mary Davis's files, along with Stephen LaRue's and Paul Hale's, contain the majority of women's magazine files. Davis's records track the finances during dummy production and market testing. Records include balance sheets, invoices, and interoffice memoranda regarding production costs estimates, circulation estimates, and notes on a presentation regarding the possible launch.
  Restricted materials include agreements or contracts with Time Inc. as a party.
  Organized chronologically based on the original order.
  - Life Special Reports: The Rep House Inc. / Paul Belanger [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Offsite-box R68)
  - Women's Magazine: General, 1976-1977 (Offsite-box 3735, Folder 11)
  - Women's Magazine: Profits and Losses, 1977 April (Offsite-box 3735, Folder 12-13)
  - Women's Magazine: Profits and Losses, 1977 May (Offsite-box 3735, Folder 14)
  - Women's Magazine: Dummy, 1977 August (Offsite-box 3735, Folder 15)
  - Women's Magazine: Profits and Losses, 1977 August (Offsite-box 3735, Folder 16)
  - Women's Magazine: Profits and Losses, 1977 October (Offsite-box 3735, Folder 17)
  - Women's Magazine: Dummy, 1977 October-November (Offsite-box 3735, Folder 18)
  - Women's Magazine: Profits and Losses, 1977 December (Offsite-box 3736, Folder 1)
  - Women's Magazine: General, 1977 (Offsite-box 3736, Folder 2)
  - Women's Magazine: Additional 100m Study, 1977 (Offsite-box 3736, Folder 3)
  - Women's Magazine: Biweekly, 1977 (Offsite-box 3736, Folder 4)
  - Women's Magazine: Photograph-Process Letter Orders, 1977 (Offsite-box 3736, Folder 5)
  - Women's Magazine: Young & Rubicam, 1977-1978 (Offsite-box 3736, Folder 6)
  - Women's Magazine: General, 1978 (Offsite-box 3736, Folder 7)
- Series I.B.7. 1973 to 1978 Business and Publishing: Business Office General Files, 1967-1978; 2.5 Linear feet in 3 record cartons
  Mainly records from general managers Winston Cox and Deane Raley as well as Raley's secretary Donna Vecchio regarding reviving Life along with business files for publishing Life Special Reports. Includes files from Life general manager John Watters on earlier specials. Records focus on advertising, circulation, distribution, finances, and publicity.
  One Day in the Life of America includes a folder called "Kunhardt file" which includes editorial material such as cable reports, daily notes, ideas from reporters, photograph ideas, and ideas from outsiders including senators. Possibly Kunhardt shared this material with the business side for reference.
  Organized alphabetically. Life Special Reports have general files in front followed by magazine issue files organized by date of publication.
  - Life: Best of Life, 1973 (Offsite-box 3736, Folder 8)
  - Life: Life History of the U.S., 1974 (Offsite-box 3736, Folder 9)
  - Life: Permissions, 1973 (Offsite-box 3736, Folder 10)
  - Life: Special Projects, 1975 (Offsite-box 3736, Folder 11)
  - Life: Use of Logo, 1974 (Offsite-box 3736, Folder 12)
  - Life: Village Voice Article [empty], circa 1977 (Offsite-box 3736, Folder 13)
  - Life: Watergate, 1973 (Offsite-box 3736, Folder 14)
  - Life Special Reports: General, 1974-1975 (Offsite-box 3736, Folder 15)
  - Life Special Reports: One Shot Future Ideas, 1973-1974 (Offsite-box 3736, Folder 16)
  - Life Special Reports: One Shot Title Research, 1973 (Offsite-box 3736, Folder 17)
  - Life Special Reports: Operating Statements, 1974-1977 (Offsite-box 3736, Folder 18)
  - Life Special Reports: Orders Sent and Receipts of Payment, 1978 (Offsite-box 3736, Folder 19)
  - Life Special Reports: Single Copy Orders, 1977-1978 (Offsite-box 3736, Folder 20)
  - Life Special Reports: To Be Billed, 1978 (Offsite-box 3736, Folder 21)
  - Life Special Reports: Term Project, 1974 (Offsite-box 3736, Folder 22)
  - Life Special Reports: Israel's Swift Victory (John Watter files), 1967-1968 (Offsite-box 3736, Folder 23)
  - Life Special Reports: The Kennedys (John Watter files), 1968 (Offsite-box 3736, Folder 24)
  - Life Special Reports: Woodstock (John Watter files), 1969 (Offsite-box 3736, Folder 25)
  - Life Special Reports: To the Moon and Back (John Watter files), 1969-1970 (Offsite-box 3736, Folder 26)
  - Life Special Reports: The Spirit of Israel, 1973 (Offsite-box 3736, Folder 27-35)
  - Life Special Reports: Year in Pictures 1973, 1973-1974 (Offsite-box 3736, Folder 36-44)
  - Life Special Reports: Year in Pictures 1973, 1973-1974 (Offsite-box 3737, Folder 1-5)
  - Life Special Reports: One Day in the Life of America, 1974-1975 (Offsite-box 3737, Folder 6-19)
  - Life Special Reports: Year in Pictures (1974), 1974-1975 (Offsite-box 3737, Folder 20-26)
  - Life Special Reports: Bicentennial Issue: The 100 Events That Shaped America, 1974-1976 (Offsite-box 3737, Folder 27-40)
  - Life Special Reports: Bicentennial Issue: The 100 Events That Shaped America, 1975 (Offsite-box 3738, Folder 1-8)
  - Life Special Reports: Year in Pictures (1975) (Offsite-box 3738, Folder 9-14)
  - Life Special Reports: Remarkable American Women, 1975-1977 (Offsite-box 3738, Folder 15-17)
  - Life Special Reports: Year in Pictures (1976), 1976-1977 (Offsite-box 3738, Folder 18-19)
  - Life Special Reports: Year in Pictures (1977) (Offsite-box 3738, Folder 20)
- Series II.A.1.a. 1981 to 1986 Editorial: Editor David Maness Files, 1981-1983; 0.1 Linear feet in 1 folder
  David Maness began his editorial career at Time Inc. in 1964. His first position was as an Articles Editor for Life, and he remained with this magazine in various editorial positions until it ceased publication in 1972. Maness transferred to Time-Life Books. In 1981 he was promoted to head of editorial of the newly reinstated Magazine Development Group. Maness remained in this position until 1984 when he became Assistant Corporate Editor.
  David Maness's files contain only his folder on the development of "a weekly advisory from the editorial rooms of Money Magazine." The majority of his Magazine Development Group files are with his Corporate Editorial files. Some of his records were passed down to Marshall Loeb when Loeb took over as the head of editorial.
  Series is a single folder.
  - MoneyLetter (newsletter), 1981-1983 (Offsite-box 3743, Folder 1)
- Series II.A.1.b. 1981 to 1986 Editorial: Editor Marshall Loeb Files, 1981-1986; 5.8 Linear feet in 7 record cartons.
  Marshall Loeb was a writer and editor at Time Inc. from 1956 to 1994. After holding positions at Time, Loeb became managing editor at Money in 1980. Starting in 1984, Loeb took over as the head of editorial for the Magazine Development Group while maintaining his managing editor role. A November 5, 1985 letter from Loeb to Fred Gruin in his Corporate Editorial files states Loeb is on a temporary assignment acting as assistant to Time Inc. editor-in-chief Henry Grunwald. Loeb's files show that he held these three positions simultaneously from around 1984 to 1986. In 1986 he became the managing editor of Fortune where he remained until his retirement in 1994.
  Miscellaneous: Special Assistant to the Editor-in-Chief Marshall Loeb Files: Time Inc. Corporate Editorial Records, MS 3009-RG 6, New-York Historical Society.
  Personnel and Organization: Department Head Lists. Time Inc. Reference Files, MS 3009-RG 3, New-York Historical Society.
  Marshall Loeb's files contain his work heading the editorial side of the department including office files and slides of magazines under development.
  Arrangement Note
  Subseries II.A.b.i. Office Files
  Subseries II.A.b.ii. Slides
  - Subseries II.A.b.i. Office Files, 1981-1986; 2.5 Linear feet in 3 record cartons
    Marshall Loeb's office files contain his work heading the editorial side of the department. His files contain some material passed down by his predecessor David Maness possibly for reference purposes. The file on background about the group includes general information that Loeb would need to take over the role including the status of projects, staff assigned, and ideas submitted. His other files contains information on magazine proposals, specifics on the contents of magazines in development, and dicussion about publication schedules.
    Some of his Magazine Development Group files were included with his Corporate Editorial files since he held these positions at the same time.
    - Background Information on Group, 1982-1984 (Offsite-box 3743, Folder 2)
    - Computer Disks, circa 1985 (Offsite-box 3743, Folder 3)
      20 computer discs (floppy disk): 5 1/4 in. with the titles of various magazines under development.
    - Concept Proposals and Testing, 1984 (Offsite-box 3743, Folder 4-5)
    - Contract Form Letter, 1983-1984? (Offsite-box 3743, Folder 6)
    - Home Office, 1984-1986 (Offsite-box 3743, Folder 7)
    - Investment Week, 1984? (Offsite-box 3743, Folder 8-9)
    - Investment Week, 1984-1985 (Offsite-box 3743, Folder 10-12)
    - Leisure: General, 1984-1985 (Offsite-box 3743, Folder 13)
    - Leisure: General, 1984-1986 (Offsite-box 3743, Folder 14-15)
    - Leisure: Meeting, 1986 January 31 (Offsite-box 3743, Folder 16)
    - Magazine Development Meeting, 1985 December 3 (Offsite-box 3744, Folder 1)
    - Magazine Ideas: General, 1984 (Offsite-box 3744, Folder 2-3)
    - Magazine Ideas: Access, 1984 (Offsite-box 3744, Folder 4)
    - Magazine Ideas: Ahead, 1984-1985 (Offsite-box 3744, Folder 5)
    - Magazine Ideas: Children/Youth, 1984 (Offsite-box 3744, Folder 6)
    - Magazine Ideas: Food, 1984 (Offsite-box 3744, Folder 7)
    - Magazine Ideas: Health/Fitness, 1984 (Offsite-box 3744, Folder 8)
    - Magazine Ideas: Home Office, 1984-1985 (Offsite-box 3744, Folder 9)
    - Magazine Ideas: Memoranda, 1984 (Offsite-box 3744, Folder 10)
    - Magazine Ideas: Men/Women, 1984 (Offsite-box 3744, Folder 11)
    - Magazine Ideas: Outside Time Inc., 1984-1985 (Offsite-box 3744, Folder 12-13)
    - Magazine Ideas: Pets, 1984 (Offsite-box 3744, Folder 14)
    - Mailings, circa 1985 (Offsite-box 3744, Folder 15)
    - Older Readers Magazines, 1981-1985 (Offsite-box 3744, Folder 16-17)
    - Picture Week: General, 1981-1985 (Offsite-box 3744, Folder 18-20)
    - Picture Week: General, 1985-1986 (Offsite-box 3745, Folder 1-3)
    - Picture Week: Cover Evaluation Study, 1985? (Offsite-box 3745, Folder 4)
    - Picture Week: Final Month, 1986 (Offsite-box 3745, Folder 5)
    - Picture Week: Test Press Kit, 1985 (Offsite-box 3745, Folder 6)
    - Protespectuses, 1984-1985 (Offsite-box 3745, Folder 7)
    - Quality: General, 1985-1986 (Offsite-box 3745, Folder 8)
    - Quality: Direct Mail Test Results, 1986 (Offsite-box 3745, Folder 9)
    - Quality: Walter Bernard Comments, 1984 (Offsite-box 3745, Folder 10)
    - Starza, Incorporated: Black Insight Business Plan, 1985 (Offsite-box 3745, Folder 11-12)
  - Subseries II.A.b.ii. Slides, 1983-circa 1985; 3.3 Linear feet in 4 record cartons
    Slides are in carousels and include page layouts or images of pages of dummies for magazines under development.
    Organized alphabetically by magazine title with notes about the materials at the front.
    - Transfer Note, 1986 (Offsite-box 3746, Folder 1)
    - Advance, circa 1985 (Offsite-box 3746, Item 1)
    - Flash (women's magazine) and Good Cook, circa 1985 (Offsite-box 3746, Item 2)
    - Home Office, circa 1985 (Offsite-box 3746, Item 3-4)
    - Investment Week, circa 1985 (Offsite-box 3746, Item 5)
    - Leisure, circa 1985 (Offsite-box 3747, Item 1)
    - Picture Week I, circa 1985 (Offsite-box 3747, Item 2)
    - Picture Week II, circa 1985 (Offsite-box 3747, Item 3)
    - Quality I, circa 1985 (Offsite-box 3747, Item 4)
    - Quality II, circa 1985 (Offsite-box 3747, Item 5)
    - Quality (Vignelli), circa 1985 (Offsite-box 3748, Item 1)
    - Then and Now, circa 1985 (Offsite-box 3748, Item 2-3)
    - Together (Live Dummy), 1983 (Offsite-box 3748, Item 4)
    - Together (Scher), circa 1983 (Offsite-box 3748, Item 5)
    - Total Health, circa 1985 (Offsite-box 3749, Item 1)
    - Woman, circa 1985 (Offsite-box 3749, Item 2)
- Series II.A.1.c. 1981 to 1986 Editorial: Editor Mark Mulvoy Files, 1982-1986; 05. Linear feet in 1 record carton
  According to his bio file, Mark Mulvoy was the deputy to Editor-in-Chief Henry Grunwald and Magazine Development editor from April to October 1986, taking over from Marshall Loeb. He was on loan from his regular role as Managing Editor of Sports Illustrated.
  Citation:
  Time Inc. Bio Files, MS 3009-RG 2, New-York Historical Society.
  Mark Mulvoy's files contain his work heading the editorial side of the department. Some Mulvoy materials span from before his tenure and contain records from his predecessor Marshall Loeb. Records include magazine proposals and feedback on magazine ideas and magazines in development.
  Organized alphabetically with general files at the front.
  - General, 1985-1986 (Offsite-box 3745, Folder 13-14)
  - Focus Group Reports: Asset and Money People, 1986 (Offsite-box 3745, Folder 15)
  - Focus Group Reports: Currents, 1986 (Offsite-box 3745, Folder 16)
  - Focus Group Reports: 50-Plus Market, 1986 (Offsite-box 3745, Folder 17)
  - Magazine Ideas: Ames, Wilmer, 1985-1986 (Offsite-box 3745, Folder 18)
  - Outside Ideas, 1986 (Offsite-box 3745, Folder 19-20)
  - Pending, 1982-1986 (Offsite-box 3745, Folder 21)
- Series II.A.2. 1981-1986 Editorial: Deputy Editor Frank Lalli Files, 1984; 0.1 Linear feet in 2 folders
  Deputy Editor Frank Lalli's files contain his administrative files with notes evaluating art directors from magazines within and outside of Time Inc. and on hiring and overseeing summer interns in the Magazine Development Group.
  - Art Directors [RESTRICTED], 1984? (Offsite-box R68)
  - Summer Interns, 1984 (Offsite-box 3750, Folder 1)
- Series II.A.3. 1981-1986 Editorial: Picture Editor Michelle Salzano McNally Files, 1984-1985; 1 Linear feet in 1 record carton
  Michelle Salzano McNally's files document her work finding images to use in all magazines under development and include some material from Picture Editor Charlie Holland. Records include correspondence returning images to the owners or licensers; and lists of photographers, photographic cooperatives, and other suppliers of images used by the Magazine Development Group including the Time Inc. Picture Collection.
  Organized alphabetically with general material at the front.
  - General, 1984 (Offsite-box 3750, Folder 2-6)
  - Image Returns, 1984-1985 (Offsite-box 3750, Folder 7-11)
  - Leisure: General, 1984-1985 (Offsite-box 3750, Folder 12)
  - Leisure: Cover Credits, circa 1985 (Offsite-box 3750, Folder 13)
  - Leisure: Material Used, 1985 (Offsite-box 3750, Folder 14)
  - Leisure: Record of Returns, 1984-1985 (Offsite-box 3750, Folder 15-16)
- Series II.A.4. 1981 to 1986 Editorial: Picture Week Files, 1984-1986, 2003; 7.75 Linear feet in 8 record cartons
  Richard Stolley proposed Picture Week in September 1981 in a memorandum to the corporate editorial team. His proposal suggested it as a black-and-white "true picture magazine" that would choose from all the photographs produced in the world that week including from freelancers, agencies, other magazines, and amateurs. He said it "would not compete with People because it would concentrate on events more than personalities, not with Life because it would be newsy and black and white, not with Time because it would have neither color nor many words." Stolley's rewrite of the prospectus in July 1985 did not deviate much from his original idea.
  Stolley's initial proposal suggested Time Inc. print an issue to try out on the newsstand to gauge demand for a picture magazine. Beginning in 1984, the Magazine Development Group conducted focus groups and test runs of Picture Week. November 17, 1986 was the final test issue. Picture Week was not published beyond testing due to concerns about the advertising market and it competing with People.
  Picture Week Files include carbon files of article research, drafts, and layouts for the dummy issues along with copies of the dummies and test run issues.
  Subseries II.A.4.a. Carbon Files
  Subseries II.A.4.b. Dummies and Test Run Issues
  - Subseries II.A.4.a.. Carbon Files, 1984-1985; 6.5 Linear feet in 7 record cartons
    Carbon Files includes the editorial production files created while designing and writing the Picture Week dummy issues. Time Inc. publications created a carbon file for every article comprising all the collected research.
    These carbon files include drafts of articles, page layouts, and cables from reporters that look intended for other Time Inc. magazines. Records are mainly from the Picture Week chief of reporters Marta Dorion, but other records come from deputy chief of reporters Joan Feeney, assistant managing editor Richard Burgheim, senior editor Steve Robinson, reporter/researchers Cinda Siler and Susan Yanella, and writers Louise Lague and David Hiltbrand.
    Some files have close or publication dates from before the first known dummy printed on May 13, 1985, and the work may have been held for later use. Reporting records for the final issue are in Marshall Loeb's files.
    Files are organized chronologically by issue close date or publication date, whichever date is available, then alphabetically by folder title which is either the article title or subject.
    - General, 1984 (Offsite-box 3754, Folder 1-7)
    - Lague, Louise, 1984 (Offsite-box 3754, Folder 8)
    - Sikh Text, 1984? (Offsite-box 3754, Folder 9)
    - Dummy, 1985 April 16 (Offsite-box 3754, Folder 10-23)
    - Dummy, 1985 April 22 (Offsite-box 3754, Folder 24)
    - Dummy, 1985 April 23 (Offsite-box 3755, Folder 1-26)
    - Dummy, 1985 April 29 (Offsite-box 3755, Folder 27)
    - Dummy, 1985 April 30 (Offsite-box 3755, Folder 28-34)
    - Dummy, 1985 May 6 (Offsite-box 3755, Folder 35-43)
    - Dummy, 1985 May 13 (Offsite-box 3756, Folder 1-22)
    - Dummy, 1985 May 13 (Offsite-box 3757, Folder 1-3)
    - Dummy, 1985 June 4 (Offsite-box 3757, Folder 4)
    - Dummy, 1985 June 17 (Offsite-box 3757, Folder 5)
    - Dummy, 1985 July 6 (Offsite-box 3757, Folder 6-10)
    - Dummy, 1985 July 30 (Offsite-box 3757, Folder 11-32)
    - Dummy, 1985 August 5 (Offsite-box 3757, Folder 33-36)
      Includes a copy of issue 1 of The Official Band Aid Magazine.
    - Dummy, 1985 August 5 (Offsite-box 3758, Folder 1-21)
    - Dummy, 1985 August 6 (Offsite-box 3758, Folder 22-30)
    - Dummy, 1985 August 6 (Offsite-box 3759, Folder 1-11)
    - Dummy, 1985 August 12 (Offsite-box 3759, Folder 12-16)
    - Dummy, 1985 August 19 (Offsite-box 3759, Folder 17-20)
    - Dummy, 1985 August 19 (Offsite-box 3760, Folder 1-12)
  - Subseries II.A.4.b. Dummies and Test Run Issues, 1984-1986, 2003; 1.25 Linear feet in 2 record cartons
    Dummies and Test Run Issues contain four different paste ups created prior to full production of the dummies, dummies from four dates of publication, and issues from two separate test runs. The dummies and test run issues show several cover design variations and logos with a major logo revision from the first test run to the second along with a price drop. Dummy dated June 17, 1985 has four different cover designs. Additional cover and logo designs are in the Art Department Graphic Development Files.
    Arranged chronologically by creation date with notes from the Time Inc. Archives regarding the materials at the front.
    - Time Inc. Archives Notes, 2003 (Offsite-box 3760, Folder 13)
    - Pre-dummy Paste Up, 1984 (Offsite-box 3760, Folder 14)
    - Pre-dummy Paste Up, 1984 May 21 (Offsite-box 3760, Folder 15)
    - Pre-dummy Paste Up, 1984 November 19 (Offsite-box 3760, Folder 16)
    - Pre-dummy Paste Up, 1984 November 19 (Offsite-box 3761, Folder 1)
    - Dummies, 1985 May 13 (Offsite-box 3761, Folder 2)
    - Dummies, 1985 June 17 (Offsite-box 3761, Folder 3-4)
    - Dummies, 1985 August 12-19 (Offsite-box 3761, Folder 5)
    - First Test Run Issues, 1985 September 30 (Offsite-box 3761, Folder 6)
    - First Test Run Issues, 1985 October 7-14 (Offsite-box 3761, Folder 7)
    - First Test Run Issues, 1985 21-28 (Offsite-box 3761, Folder 8)
    - First Test Run Issues, 1985 November 4-25 (Offsite-box 3761, Folder 9)
    - First Test Run Issues, 1985 December 2-23 (Offsite-box 3761, Folder 10)
    - First Test Run Issues, 1985 December 30-1986 February 3 (Offsite-box 3761, Folder 11)
    - Second Test Run Issues, 1986 July 28-September 8 (Offsite-box 3761, Folder 12)
    - Second Test Run Issues, 1986 September 15-29 (Offsite-box 3761, Folder 13)
    - Second Test Run Issues, 1986 November 6-November 17 (Offsite-box 3761, Folder 14)
- Series II.A.5. Art Department: Graphic Development Files, 1985-1986; 3.75 Linear feet in 1 record carton and 3 flat boxes